Who said the countryside was peaceful?
Peter Rabbit is a animation, adventure, family film directed by Will Gluck.
Peter Rabbit's feud with Mr.
McGregor escalates to greater heights than ever before as they rival for the
affections of the warm-hearted animal lover who lives next door.
Peter Rabbit (voice), played by James Corden.
Beatrix 'Bea' Potter / Jemima Puddle-Duck (voice), played by Rose Byrne.
Thomas McGregor / Mr. Jeremy Fisher (voice), played by Domhnall Gleeson.
Flopsy Rabbit / Narrator (voice), played by Margot Robbie.
Mopsy Rabbit (voice), played by Elizabeth Debicki.
Cottontail Rabbit (voice), played by Daisy Ridley.
Peter Rabbit is a 2018 live-action animated comedy film based on the
character from The Tale of Peter Rabbit by Beatrix Potter.
It was directed by Will Gluck and written by Gluck and Rob Lieber.
The film stars Rose Byrne, Domhnall Gleeson, Sam Neill, and Marianne Jean-Baptiste in live-action roles; Byrne, Gleeson, and Neill also voice animated
characters, in addition to the voices of Margot Robbie as Flopsy Rabbit and the narrator, and James Corden as the titular character.
The film follows  Peter Rabbit as he deals with new problems when the late Mr.
McGregor's great nephew arrives and discovers the
trouble Peter's family can get into.
Peter Rabbit had its world premiere at The Grove on February 3, 2018.
It was released in the United States of America on February 9, 2018, in the
United Kingdom on March 16, 2018, and in Australia on March 22, 2018.
The film received mixed reviews from critics, mainly for
its deviations from the source material.
It grossed $351 million worldwide on a $50 million budget.
A sequel, Peter Rabbit 2: The Runaway, was released in 2021 without the involvement of
Sony Pictures Animation, but did not gross as much as the first film.
The film explores themes of human animal relationship, based on children's
book, rabbit, duringcreditsstinger, live action and animation.